HOWARD: I really don't think
the colonoscopy was necessary.
(Leonard:)Before you got all swollen up...
...I thought you're trying to keep me out
of the apartment...
(Leonard:)...so you could throw me
a surprise party.
(Howard:)Oh, right, it's your birthday.
(Howard:)I had no idea it was your birthday.
I forgot.
(Howard:)What a lousy way to spend a birthday.
Well, it's all over now.
There is a party, isn't there?
(Leonard:)Maybe.
(Leonard:)Howard.
- Are you mad?
- How could I be mad?
(Leonard:)You actually risked your life
because you care about me.
(Howard:)Yeah, that's why I did it.
All right, here we go.
(Leonard:)My first birthday party.
[SINGING CYNDI LAUPER'S
"TRUE COLORS"]
I see your true colors
And that's why I love you